https://www.proformanceunlimited.com/privacy-policy/

FollowFollowFollowFollow
Reliable, Custom Built Crate Performance EnginesToll Free 1-800-267-3940 Info@proformanceunlimited.com
Proformance Unlimited Privacy Policy
Thank you for visiting our web site. This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.
Collection of Information
We collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. The information you provide is used to fulfill you specific request. This information is only used to fulfill your specific request, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner, for example to add you to one of our mailing lists.
Cookie/Tracking Technology
The Site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.
Distribution of Information
We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes.
Commitment to Data Security
Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings.
Privacy Contact Information
If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:
By e-mail: info@proformanceunlimited.com
By Phone: 1-800-267-3940
Contact:
733 North Drive
Suite B
Melbourne, FL 32934
PH: 800-267-3940
Info@proformanceunlimited.com
Shop Hours:
Mon–Thur 8am – 4pm EST
Friday 8am – 3pm EST
Phone Hours:
Mon–Thur 8am – 5pm EST
Friday 8am – 3pm EST
Helpful Links:
Warranty
Marine Warranty
Cancellation/Return
Policy/Privacy Policy
About Us
FollowFollowFollowFollow
PROFORMANCE UNLIMITED INC. RESERVES THE RIGHT TO MAKE CHANGES IN DESIGN OR TO MAKE ADDITIONS TO OR IMPROVEMENTS UPON ANY OF ITS PRODUCTS AT ANY TIME WITHOUT INCURRING ANY OBLIGATION WHATSOEVER TO INSTALL THE SAME OR IMPROVEMENT UPON PRODUCTS PREVIOUSLY MANUFACTURED. OCCASIONALLY DEPENDING ON AVAILABILITY, PARTS MAY BE SUBSTITUTED THAT WILL NOT EFFECT PRICE, PERFORMANCE, APPEARANCE OR QUALITY OF THE PRODUCT.*Engine shown with optional upgrades
